[{"answer": "The sax player", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-English-Patient.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yeah", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Box of raisinettes eating another box of raisinettes? It's perverse", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-English-Patient.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Why's he dating a that place? They're not having children", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Got my umbrella", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-English-Patient.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Hot and spicy", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-English-Patient.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yes I am", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Ugh. You wouldn't believe it. My boyfriend dumped me. My friends, who I don't even like, they won't talk to me.  All because I don't like that stupid English Patient movie", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-English-Patient.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Oh, come on. Good? What was good about it?  Those sex scenes! I mean, please! Gimme something I can use", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " So she wanted you to come up, but you left because you thought some guy might be calling you?! my friend puts his bag in the bedroom and returns as my friend paces the floor", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-English-Patient.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " my friend, you've got my friend. Forget about my friend. You've ou", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "my friend, your palate's unrefined", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-English-Patient.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Is too", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Is not", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-English-Patient.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Is not", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Is too", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-English-Patient.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Is too", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I'm not having this conversation", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-English-Patient.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Am not", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Are too", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-English-Patient.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Are too", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Am not", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-English-Patient.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Am not", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "my friend, what'd you think", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-English-Patient.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " You haven't seen it", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I got married in high school", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-English-Patient.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "This is my friend's kid", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " We're talking about people, right", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-English-Patient.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I thought he quit smoking cigars", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well, yeah, yeah. But they also rolled for his brother...  ...my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-English-Patient.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Uh, my friend", "qsentId": 32}]